. 。
.  。
Bunny,
الأرنب
this is the dorm specially prepared by the business school
هذا هو المسكن الذي تم إعداده خصيصًا من قبل كلية إدارة الأعمال
for teaching assistants with excellent working ability.
لمساعدي التدريس بقدرة عمل ممتازة.
Although the environment looks simple,
على الرغم من أن البيئة تبدو بسيطة ،
here,
هنا،
But it represents the glorious history of Ouyang's family.
لكنه يمثل التاريخ المجيد لعائلة أويانغ.
There have been so many years of ups and downs.
كانت هناك سنوات عديدة من الصعود والهبوط.
This is what you call
هذا ما تسمونه
a comfortable office environment,
بيئة مكتبية مريحة ،
Bunny,
الأرنب
do you think I'm lying to you?
هل تعتقد انني اكذب عليك
Or do you think the environment here is not good?
أم أنك تعتقد أن البيئة هنا ليست جيدة؟
None of them.
لا احد منهم.
I just think,
فقط افكر،
if a teaching assistant lives in such a big house,
إذا كان مدرس يعيش في مثل هذا المنزل الكبير ،
It's a bit gloomy here.
إنه قاتم بعض الشيء هنا.
There's a clue to the Heart of Stallone hidden in this house,
هناك دليل على قلب ستالون مخبأ في هذا المنزل
and you're dead if you fool me.
وأنت ميت إذا خدعتني.
Please
لو سمحت
Ouyang Yuchuan,
أويانغ يوتشوان ،
what are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Moving out?
أرحل؟
You want to live here too?
هل تريد أن تعيش هنا أيضًا؟
Oh sorry,
أه آسف،
I forgot to tell you just now,
لقد نسيت أن أخبرك الآن ،
Interesting.
مثير للاهتمام.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Fox.
فوكس.
Su Shengnan,
سو شنغنان ،
what do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Didn't you say you don't like him?
ألم تقل أنك لا تحبه؟
Why are you with him?
لماذا انت معه
I just moved two days ago,
لقد انتقلت للتو منذ يومين ،
and Miss Leng found out so soon.
واكتشفت الآنسة لينغ ذلك قريبًا.
Why do you care so much about me?
لماذا تهتم بي كثيرا؟
I'll give you one last chance.
سأعطيك فرصة أخيرة.
What's your relationship?
ما علاقتك؟
What's my relationship with him?
ما علاقتي به؟
What does it have to do with you?
ما علاقة ذلك بك؟
Why are you so shameless?
لماذا أنت وقح جدا؟
Sit down.
اجلس.
Let's have a heart-to-heart talk,
دعونا نجري حديثًا من القلب إلى القلب ،
Come on, tell me about you,
هيا اخبرني عنك
the handsome Miss Leng,
الآنسة الوسيم لينغ ،
A big star with millions of fans,
نجم كبير مع ملايين المعجبين ،
who is so beautiful,
من هو جميل جدا
Your pursuers went from Tokyo to Rome.
مطاردوك ذهبوا من طوكيو إلى روما.
What do you like about Ouyang Yuchuan?
ما الذي يعجبك في Ouyang Yuchuan؟
That's right.
صحيح.
What do I like about him?
ماذا يعجبني فيه؟
You like him?
أنت معجب به؟
It's just a setup.
إنه مجرد إعداد.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
the plot was unreasonable from the very beginning.
المؤامرة كانت غير معقولة منذ البداية.
No.
لا.
I just like him.
أنا أحبه فقط.
He's good everywhere.
إنه جيد في كل مكان.
If you don't like him, don't pester him.
إذا كنت لا تحبه ، فلا تضايقه.
Get off.
ترجل.
Then I'll trouble you
ثم سوف أزعجك
to keep him away from me.
لإبعاده عني.
I'm sick of it.
أنا مريض منه.
You.
أنت.
I heard that you moved into our old house,
سمعت أنك انتقلت إلى منزلنا القديم ،
and disbanded the waiters and bodyguards.
وحل النوادل والحراس الشخصيين.
Yes
نعم
Yuchuan,
يوتشوان ،
you can't be so casual anymore.
لا يمكنك أن تكون غير رسمي بعد الآن.
How can you call strangers to live in an ancient mansion?
كيف يمكنك استدعاء الغرباء للعيش في قصر قديم؟
The current environment of the old mansion is not suitable for you to live in,
البيئة الحالية للقصر القديم غير مناسبة لك للعيش فيها ،
Yuchuan,
يوتشوان ،
You can't be willful anymore.
لا يمكنك أن تكون عنيدًا بعد الآن.
You'd better come back.
من الأفضل أن تعود.
Thank you, Grandma.
شكرا لك جدتي.
During this period, Miss Su taught me a lot,
خلال هذه الفترة ، علمتني الآنسة سو الكثير ،
that I'm not who I used to be.
أنني لست كما اعتدت أن أكون.
You and Leng Yan are engaged?
أنت و Leng Yan مخطوبان؟
Why are you still not clear with her?
لماذا ما زلت غير واضح معها؟
If such a thing gets out,
إذا خرج مثل هذا الشيء ،
where will our Ouyang family put their face?
أين ستضع عائلتنا اويانغ وجوههم؟
Yuchuan, you'd better leave that silly girl.
يوتشوان ، من الأفضل أن تترك تلك الفتاة السخيفة.
Are you worthy of Yanyan?
هل تستحق يانيان؟
My marriage with Miss Leng,
زواجي مع الآنسة لينغ ،
was decided by you on your own when I was a child.
كنت قد قررت بنفسك عندما كنت طفلة.
You all know that I don't like her at all.
تعلمون جميعًا أنني لا أحبها على الإطلاق.
It's even more impossible to marry her.
بل من المستحيل الزواج منها.
In Ouyang's family,
في عائلة أويانغ ،
marriage is never up to you juniors.
الزواج لا يعود لكم ابدا صغار.
Behind every marriage,
وراء كل زواج
the Ouyang family's future is at stake.
مستقبل عائلة أويانغ على المحك.
Just like the marriage between your grandma and me,
تمامًا مثل الزواج بين جدتك وأنا ،
the great Ouyang family has achieved even higher success.
لقد حققت عائلة Ouyang العظيمة نجاحًا أكبر.
Father,
أب،
I suddenly feel so pitiful.
فجأة أشعر بالشفقة.
Look at this kid.
انظر إلى هذا الطفل.
You're used to it.
أنت معتاد على ذلك.
Nice.
لطيف - جيد.
Ouyang Yuchuan,
أويانغ يوتشوان ،
I knew it was you.
كنت أعلم أنه أنت.
It's boring.
انها مملة.
How do you know
كيف علمت بذلك
I didn't teach you enough
أنا لم أعلمك ما يكفي
last time?
آخر مرة؟
Little Rabbit's lesson,
درس الأرنب الصغير ،
how can you forget it?
كيف يمكنك نسيانها
However,
لكن،
you can recognize my hand.
يمكنك التعرف على يدي.
Do you have me in your heart?
هل لديكني في قلبك؟
Look,
ينظر،
Surprise or not surprise.
مفاجأة أم لا مفاجأة.
I prepared it carefully for you.
لقد أعددته بعناية من أجلك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Bunny,
الأرنب
thank you for your appreciation.
شكرا لتقديرك.
I'll do better in the future.
سأفعل ما هو أفضل في المستقبل.
Thank you so much.
شكراً جزيلاً.
Mr. Leng,
السيد.  لينغ ،
Ouyang Yuchuan, in order to pursue Miss Su,
Ouyang Yuchuan ، لكي تطارد الآنسة Su ،
You can't help but use all means?
لا يسعك إلا استخدام كل الوسائل؟
Move into Ouyang's house
انتقل إلى منزل Ouyang
with Miss Su,
مع الآنسة سو ،
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
He said
هو قال
there was a clue to the Heart of Stallone in the old mansion.
كان هناك دليل على قلب ستالون في القصر القديم.
I see.
أرى.
I have to get the Heart of Stallone first,
يجب أن أحصل على قلب ستالون أولاً ،
I heard that Ouyang's family's secret is hidden inside,
سمعت أن سر عائلة أويانغ مخفي في الداخل ،
So you didn't look for it for Miss Su.
لذا لم تبحثي عنها لملكة جمال سو.
Not exactly.
ليس تماما.
Mr. Leng is setting a banner,
السيد لينغ يضع لافتة ،
in order to know the secret of Ouyang Family,
من أجل معرفة سر عائلة أويانغ ،
In order to get Miss Su,
من أجل الحصول على الآنسة سو ،
must
يجب
If you want to buy the old mansion,
إذا كنت ترغب في شراء القصر القديم ،